Guide to the Liberty Hyde Bailey, New York State College of Agriculture and Agricultural Experiment Station records, 1903-1914.
Liberty Hyde Bailey, New York State College of Agriculture and Agricultural Experiment Station records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Liberty Hyde Bailey, New York State College of Agriculture and Agricultural Experiment Station records, 1903-1914.
21-2-84
L. H. (Liberty Hyde) Bailey, 1858-1954.
48.7 cubic ft.
Correspondence, reports, and other files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Director's files including correspondence, committee reports, and files concerning construction projects and the general administration of the college.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Director's files including correspondence, committee reports, and files concerning construction projects and the general administration of the college.
Also, signatures from students in appreciation to Liberty Hyde Bailey, 1908.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Bailey, L. H. (Liberty Hyde), 1858-1954.; Cornell University--Administration.; New York State College of Agriculture.
Subjects:
Agriculture--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
See also Liberty Hyde Bailey Papers, #21-2-3342 and Liberty Hyde Bailey Forestry Papers, #21-2-576.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
See accession folder for a list of original box file numbers used by the donor, and for a list of missing files.
CONTAINER LIST
- Aug. 25 - Oct. 1, 1903 (Box 1)
- Oct. 1 - Nov. 5, 1903 (Box 2)
- Nov. 5 - Dec. 22, 1903 (Box 3)
- Dec. 22, 1903 - Feb. 2, 1904 (Box 4)
- Feb. 2 - Mar. 14, 1904 (Box 5)
- Mar. 14 - Apr. 18, 1904 (Box 6)
- Apr. 18 - May 18, 1904 (Box 7)
- May 18 - June 20, 1904 (Box 8)
- June 20 - Sept. 28, 1904 (Box 9)
- Sept. 28 - Oct. 30, 1904 (Box 10)
- Oct. 30 - Dec. 5, 1904 (Box 11)
- Dec. 5, 1904 - Jan. 15, 1905 (Box 12)
- Jan. 15 - Feb. 18, 1905 (Box 13)
- Feb. 18 - Mar. 25, 1905 (Box 14)
- Mar. 25 - May 8, 1905 (Box 15)
- May 8 - Aug. 1, 1905 (Box 16)
- Aug. 1 - Oct. 19, 1905 (Box 17)
- Oct. 19 - Dec. 2, 1905 (Box 18)
- Dec. 2, 1905 - Jan. 16, 1906 (Box 19)
- Jan. 16 - Feb. 23, 1906 (Box 20)
- Feb. 23 - Apr. 5, 1906 (Box 21)
- Apr. 5 - May 21, 1906 (Box 22)
- May 21 - July 30, 1906 (Box 23)
- July 30 - Sept. 6, 1906 (Box 24)
- Sept. 6 - Oct. 15, 1906 (There are some items dated 1907) (Box 25)
- Oct. 16 - Nov. 1, 1906 (Box 26)
- Nov. 2 - Dec. 1, 1906 (Box 27)
- Dec. 2, 1906 - Jan. 1, 1907 (Box 28)
- Jan. 2 - Jan. 27, 1907 (Box 29)
- Jan. 28 - Feb. 28, 1907 (Box 30)
- Mar. 1 - 15, 1907 (Box 31)
- Mar. 16 - Apr. 5, 1907 (Box 32)
- Apr. 6 - May 6, 1907 (Box 33)
- May 6 - June 10, 1907 (Box 34)
- June 11 - July 10, 1907 (Box 35)
- July 11 - 31, 1907 [incl. Aug. 1, Aug. 5] (Box 36)
- Aug. 1-20, 1907 (Box 37)
- Aug. 21 - Sept. 10, 1907 (Box 38)
- Sept. 11 - Oct. 8, 1907 (Box 39)
- Oct. 8 - 31, 1907 (Box 40)
- Nov. 1-20, 1907 (Box 41)
- Nov. 20 - Dec. 10, 19C7 (Box 42)
- Dec. 11 - 31, 1907 (Box 43)
- Jan. 1 - 20, 1908 (Box 44)
- Jan. 21 - Feb. 15, 1908 (Box 45)
- Feb. 16 - Mar. 5, 1908 (Box 46)
- Mar. 6-31, 1908 (Box 47)
- Apr. 1-21, 1908 (Box 48)
- Apr. 22 - May 16, 1908 (Box 49)
- May 17 - June 14, 1908 (Box 50)
- June 15 - July 6, 1908 * (Box 51)
- Mar. 3-20, 1909 (Box 52)
- Mar. 21 - 31, 1909 (Box 53)
- Apr. 1-15, 1909 (Box 54)
- Apr. 16 - May 5, 1909 (Box 55)
- May 6-20, 1909 (Box 56)
- May 21 - June 5, 1909 (Box 57)
- June 6-20, 1909 (Box 58)
- June 21 - July 14, 1909 (Box 59)
- July 15 - Aug. 10, 1909 (Box 60)
- Aug. 11 - Sept. 9, 1909 (Box 61)
- A-B, Sept. 10 - Dec. 31, 1909 (Box 62)
- C-F, Sept. 10 - Dec. 31, 1909 (Box 63)
- G-L, Sept. 10 - Dec. 31, 1909 (Box 64)
- M-Q, Sept. 10 - Dec. 31, 1909 (Box 65)
- R-S, Sept. 10 - Dec. 31, 1909 (Box 66)
- T-Z, Sept. 10 - Dec. 31, 1909 (Box 67)
- A-B, Jan. 1 - Apr. 31, 1910 (Box 68)
- C-G, Jan. 1 - Apr. 31, 1910 (Box 69)
- H-L, Jan. 1 - Apr. 31, 1910 (Box 70)
- M-P, Jan. 1 - Apr. 31, 1910 (Box 71)
- Q-S, Jan. 1 - Apr. 31, 1910 (Box 72)
- T-Z, Jan. 1 - Apr. 31, 1910 (Box 73)
- A-B, May 1 - Sept. 15, 1910 (Box 74)
- C-F, May 1 - Sept. 15, 1910 (Box 75)
- G-L, May 1 - Sept. 15, 1910 (Box 76)
- M-P, May 1 - Sept. 15, 1910 (Box 77)
- Q-S, May 1 - Sept. 15, 1910 (Box 78)
- T-Z, May 1 - Sept. 15, 1910 (Box 79)
- A-B, Sept. 16, 1910 - Jan. 31, 1911 (Box 80)
- C-F, Sept. 16, 1910 - Jan. 31, 1911 (Box 81)
- G-J, Sept. 16, 1910 - Jan. 31, 1911 (Box 82)
- K-M, Sept. 16, 1910 - Jan. 31, 1911 (Box 83)
- N-R, Sept. 16, 1910 - Jan. 31, 1911 (Box 84)
- S-T, Sept. 16, 1910 - Jan. 31, 1911 (Box 85)
- U-Z, Sept. 16, 1910 - Jan. 31, 1911 (Box 86)
- A-B, Feb. 1 - May 31, 1911 (Box 87)
- C-E, Feb. 1 - May 31, 1911 (Box 88)
- F-H, Feb. 1 - May 31, 1911 (Box 89)
- I-L, Feb. 1 - May 31, 1911 (Box 90)
- M-Pearson, Feb. 1 - May 31, 1911 (Box 91)
- Pearson-Sch, Feb. 1 - May 31, 1911 (Box 92)
- Sch-T, Feb. 1 - May 31, 1911 (Box 93)
- A-C, June 1 - Aug. 31, 1911 (Box 94)
- D-H, June 1 - Aug. 31, 1911 (Box 95)
- I -May, June 1 - Aug. 31, 1911 (Box 96)
- Me-Schu, June 1 - Aug. 31, 1911 (Box 97)
- Se-V, June 1 - Aug. 31, 1911 (Box 98)
- W-Z, June 1 - Aug. 31, 1911 (Box 99)
- A-C, Sept. 1 - Nov. 30, 1911 (Box 100)
- D-J, Sept. 1 - Nov. 30, 1911 (Box 101)
- K-O, Sept. 1 - Nov. 30, 1911 (Box 102)
- P-S, Sept. 1 - Nov. 30, 1911 (Box 103)
- T-Z, Sept. 1 - Nov. 30, 1911 (Box 104)
- A-D, Dec. 1, 1911 - Feb. 29, 1912 (Box 105)
- E-K, Dec. 1, 1911 - Feb. 29, 1912 (Box 106)
- L-O, Dec. 1, 1911 - Feb. 29, 1912 (Box 107)
- P-S, Dec. 1, 1911 - Feb. 29, 1912 (Box 108)
- T-Z, Dec. 1, 1911 - Feb. 29, 1912 (Box 109)
- A-C, Mar. 1 - May 31, 1912 (Box 110)
- D-H, Mar. 1 - May 31, 1912 (Box 111)
- I-Mi, Mar. 1 - May 31, 1912 (Box 112)
- Mo-Stoc (Box 113)
- Stone-Z, Mar. 1 - May 31, 1912 (Box 114)
- A-G, June 1 - Aug. 31, 1912 (Box 115)
- H-N, June 1 - Aug. 31, 1912 (Box 116)
- O-Z, June 1 - Aug. 31, 1912 (Box 117)
- A-C, Sept. 1 - Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 118)
- D-H, Sept. 1 - Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 119)
- I-Mann, Sept. 1 - Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 120)
- Manni-R, Sept. 1 - Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 121)
- S-Tuck, Sept. 1 - Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 122)
- Tuck-Z, Sept. 1 - Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 123)
- A-C, Jan. 1 - Mar. 31, 1913 (Box 124)
- D-J, Jan. 1 - Mar. 31, 1913 (Box 125)
- K-M, Jan. 1 - Mar. 31, 1913 (Box 126)
- N-Sti, Jan. 1 - Mar. 31, 1913 (Box 127)
- Sto-Z, Jan. 1 - Mar. 31, 1913 (Box 128)
- A-B, Apr. 1 - July 31, 1913 (Box 129)
- C-D, Apr. 1 - July 31, 1913 (Box 130)
- E-Ha, Apr. 1 - July 31, 1913 (Box 131)
- He-Lyn, Apr. 1 - July 31, 1913 (Box 132)
- Lyon-Mi, Apr. 1 - July 31, 1913 (Box 133)
- Mo-Rhi, Apr. 1 - July 31, 1913 (Box 134)
- Ric-Sti, Apr. 1 - July 31, 1913 (Box 135)
- Sto-Wil, Apr. 1 - July 31, 1913 (Box 136)
- Web-Z, Apr. 1 - July 31, 1913 (Box 137)
- A-Bond, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 138)
- Bons-Cav, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 139)
- Cen-Cur, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 140)
- D-E, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 141)
- F, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 142)
- G-Hay, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 143)
- Hayes-Hyd, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 144)
- I-Liv, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 145)
- Liv-Lyon, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 146)
- McA-Mit, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 147)
- Moh-O, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 148)
- P-Red, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 149)
- Ree-Ryd, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 150)
- Sa-Sto, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 151)
- Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 Stor-Tuck (Box 152)
- Tuck-Van R, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 153)
- Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 Van R-Wil (Box 154)
- Wil-Wing, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 155)
- Wing-Z, Aug. 1913 - Oct. 1914 (Box 156)
- Experiment Station. Projects A-P 1906-08, 1912-1913 [Filed under names of experimenters] (Box 157)
- Experiment Station Projects R-W 1906-1913 (Box 158)
- F-l Director's Private Files. 1909-1914 Poultry letters; Grounds Comm.; Landscape Art Dept.; Farm Practice and Farm Crops Dept.; Farm Bureau; County agents; Maintenance monies in other colleges, Agricultural College Council Minutes; Buildings (Box 159)
- F-2 Director's Private File 1906-1914 Farm Bureau correspondence: & memoranda, U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1906-1908, student statistics, Rural Education, Resolution on College of Agriculture bills, 1910, publications (Box 160)
- F-3 Director's Private Files 1907-1914 Old printing contracts, Poultry Dept., honor system, Alfred School, Morrisville School, miscellaneous publications (Box 161)
- LitB Misc. corr. (Box 162)
- Signatures from students in appreciation to Liberty Hyde Bailey, 1908 (Mapcase-folder 1)